Guide to the Annual Reports 1973-2009 [Call #]
Eastern Connecticut State University, Publisher
Annual Reports1973-2009
[Call #]
4 linear feet
Eastern Connecticut State University
The Annual Report Collection consists of reports submitted to the Office of the President from each department of the university in the spring semester.
Provenance
The original annual report material was sent to the University Archives from the office of President David G. Carter on July 27, 2001. It included reports from 1991-1992 through 1996-1997.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Scope and Content Note
The Annual Report Collection consists of reports submitted to the Office of the President from each department of the university in the spring semester. The first group of reports sent to the University Archives for preservation dated from 1991-1997. Earlier annual reports dating from 1973-1990 were collected from various sources and later added to the collection. Current and past reports are added as they become available. The reports appear in the order in which they were received unless otherwise indicated. Access to faculty resumes or other personalized information included in the reports is restricted.
Series I - 1973-1979; This series includes the earliest annual reports available. These include reports from the Office of Research and the School of Arts and Sciences.
Series II - 1983-1984; 1987-1989; This series includes one Special Services report for 1983-1984, 26 reports from 1987-1988 (Academic Affairs to Student Affairs) and 8 reports from 1988-1989 (Academic Affairs).
Series II - 1990-1995; This series includes annual reports submitted to the archives from the Office of the President for the 1990-91 academic year through the 1994-95 academic year.
Series III - 1995-1999; This series includes annual reports from the 1995-1996 academic year through the 1999-2000 academic year.
Series IV - 2000-2004; This series includes annual reports from the 2000-2001 academic year through 2004-2005 academic year.
Series V - 2005-2009; This series includes annual reports from the 2005-2006 through 2009-2010.
Arrangement
The reports were placed in acid-free folders and divided into series chronologically by academic year. Material is in the order in which it was received unless otherwise noted.
The files are grouped into 5 series:
Series I - 1973-1979
Series II - 1983-1995
Series III - 1995-1999
Series IV - 2000-2004
Series V - 2005-2009
Access Points
Subject Organizations:
Eastern Connecticut State University. Office of the President.
Subject Topics:
Colleges and Universities -- Administration.
Document Types:
Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Publications.; School Records.
Related Material
A collection of Annual Reports submitted to other President’s of the Connecticut University System in the late 1960’s can be found in the Office of the President - Searle F. Charles. The University Archives has a substantial collection of university archives material and also houses the Connecticut Studies Collection. For more detailed information on these collections please contact the staff member at the reference desk.
Container List
[The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.]
- Series I - 1973-1979
  - Office of Research, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Office of Research, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Series II - 1983-84; 1987-90
  - Special Services, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice-President, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions & Enrollment Planning, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs: Media, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Sciences, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Women's Center, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Affairs, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Affairs (2), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Campus Hearing/Appeals Process, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Health Services, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Housing, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Office of Student Center/Activities, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Orientation, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Personnel Administration, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Safety and Counseling, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Student Affairs, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (3), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Sciences (2), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs: Women's Center, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Associate Vice President, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Admissions and Enrollment Plan, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Advisement Center, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Institute, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center (2), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Academic Affairs: Media, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar Office, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science (2), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics and Computer Science, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Academic Affairs: School of, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Academic Affairs: Communications, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics and Management Science, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Affirmative Action, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Athletic, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Finance and Administrative, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Finance and Administrative (2), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Finance and Administrative (3), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Health Services, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Personnel Administration, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Planning and Institutional Research, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Transfer Articulation, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Series III - 1990-1994
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grants Office, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: Admission and Enrollment Planning, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Admission and Enrollment Planning (2), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Center, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar Office, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Sciences, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Sciences, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics and Management Science, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (3), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (4), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant Office, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant Office (2), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment Planning, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Academic Affairs: International Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Academic Affairs: Media, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (3), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics and Computer Science, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics and Management Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Day Care Training, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Faculty and Staff Vita, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Faculty and Staff Vita (2), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Faculty and Staff Vita (3), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Athletics, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Athletics (2), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Athletics (3), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Athletics (4), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Campus Student Judicial System, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Development, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Finance and Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Finance and Administration (2), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Finance and Administration (3), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Financial Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Health Services, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Housing Office, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - International Student, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - National Student Exchange, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Personnel Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Planning and Institutional Research, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Student Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Student Center, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Student Orientation, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Academic Affairs: Center of Education Excellence, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Institute, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Academic Affairs: International Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Center, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar Office, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (3), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Academic Affairs: English (2), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Academic Affairs: English (3), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Academic Affairs: English (4), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (3), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (4), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (5), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics and Computer Science, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Honors Program, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program (2), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program (3), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics and Management Science, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Day Care Training, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Graduate Division, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant's Office, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment Planning, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Academic Excellence, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Academic Affairs: International Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Center, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar's Office, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (3), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (4), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (3), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics and Computer Science, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs: Honors Program, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (2), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics and, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics and, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Day Care Training Program, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Health and Physical Education, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Health and Physical Education (2), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Division, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Office, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Affirmative Action, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Career and Experiential Education, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Finance and Administration, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Finance and Administrative, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Finance and Administrative, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Finance and Administration, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Finance and Administration/Fiscal Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Finance and Administration/Public Safety, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Financial Aid and Veteran Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Health Services, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Housing Office, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics (2), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics (3), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - New Student Orientation, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Office of Institutional Advancement, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Office of Public Relation, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Personnel Administration, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Planning and Institutional Research, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Student Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Student Center, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grants Officer, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions & Enrollment Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Academic Affairs: International Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (3), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Center, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar's Office, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Sciences, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (3), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (4), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (3), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (4), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (5), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics and Computer Science, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Sciences, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 78)